<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Torun_TourGuide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="copernicus">Copernicus Statue</string>
    <string name="copernicus_details">One of the most important symbols of Torun</string>
    <string name="tower">The Leaning Tower</string>
    <string name="tower_details">A medieval defensive Tower with a considerable tilt</string>
    <string name="town_hall">The Old Town Hall</string>
    <string name="hall_details">One of the largest brick buildings of that kind in Europe</string>
    <string name="copernicus_house">The Copernicus\' House</string>
    <string name="house_details">A medieval burgher\'s house belonged to Copernicus family</string>
    <string name="castle">Teutonic Knights\' Castle</string>
    <string name="castle_details">Among the oldest  structures of that kind. Its construstion began in mid 13th century</string>
    <string name="gate">The Bridge Gate</string>
    <string name="gate_details">Built in 1432, initially it was called the Crossing Gate or Ferry Gate</string>
    <string name="cathedral">SS. Johns\' Cathedral</string>
    <string name="cathedral_details">The Gothic Cathedral of St. John the Baptist and St. John the Evangelist</string>
    <string name="gingerbread">Gingerbread Museum</string>
    <string name="gingerbread_details">It is a place where the history has the smell and the taste of gingerbread adventure</string>
    <string name="convent">The Convent Gate</string>
    <string name="convent_details">Also called the Holy Spirit Gate, erected as one of four gates leading into Torun</string>
    <string name="holy_spirit">Holy Spirit Church</string>
    <string name="holy_spirit_detail">Late-Baroque edifice raised in mid-18th century as an Evangelical church</string>
    <string name="hotel1">1231 Hotel****</string>
    <string name="holtel1_details">Boutique hotel where the building combines modern décor with history of renovated 13th century Old Mill</string>
    <string name="bulwar">Hotel Bulwar****</string>
    <string name="bulwar_details">The historical building Koszary Racławickie, today\'s Hotel Bulwar, was constructed 1819–1822 as military barracks</string>
    <string name="hotel_copernicus">Copernicus Hotel****</string>
    <string name="hotel_copernicus_details">A modern and comfortably equipped object - top choice for family vacation, company meetings</string>
    <string name="mercure">Hotel Mercure****</string>
    <string name="mercure_details">Situated in the city center, close to the old town and the birthplace of Nicolaus Copernicus</string>
    <string name="filmar">Hotel Filmar****</string>
    <string name="filmar_details">An outstanding venue for conferences, business meetings and private celebrations</string>
    <string name="nova">Nova Apartamenty</string>
    <string name="nova_details">The charm of a over hundredyearold building with all the modern conveniences of a contemporary apartment</string>
    <string name="roze">Roze i Zen Apartamenty</string>
    <string name="roze_details">In the heart of the city centre with a restaurant that you must try out</string>
    <string name="freedom">Freedom Hostel</string>
    <string name="freedom_details">A really cosy and romantic place. We make sure that you feel totally at home</string>
    <string name="mcsm">MCSM Hostel</string>
    <string name="mcsm_details">A perfect place to stay longer in Toruń and spend your spare time actively</string>
    <string name="chleb">Chleb i Wino</string>
    <string name="chleb_details">Italian food with bread baked every day from their own recipe traditional way</string>
    <string name="olbracht">Jan Olbracht Old Town Brewery</string>
    <string name="olbracht_details">Here you will be able to see the beer creation process with your own eyes and taste the beverage straight from the tank</string>
    <string name="loft">Loft79</string>
    <string name="loft_details">Uniqe and modern place where you can eat delicious food in a nice family atmosphere</string>
    <string name="manekin">Manekin</string>
    <string name="manekin_details">Best pancakes in the city with all kinds of fillings. Manekin is more than just food, it\'s a lifestyle</string>
    <string name="karrotka">Karrotka</string>
    <string name="karrotka_details">Vegetarian bar</string>
    <string name="stary">Stary Torun</string>
    <string name="stary_details">Traditioal pierogi prepared on the spot. Unique interiors and home-like taste</string>
    <string name="lenkiewicz">Cafe Lenkiewicz</string>
    <string name="lenkiewicz_details">A recognized confectionery company with great coffee and delicious cakes</string>
    <string name="arkadami">Pod Arkadami</string>
    <string name="arkadami_details">This milk bar is a perfect place to eat good cheap food from polish cuisine</string>
    <string name="carpe">Carpe Kraft</string>
    <string name="carpe_details">One of three places in the city where you can taste a whole range of craft, unique and seasonal beers</string>
    <string name="skyway">Bella SkyWay</string>
    <string name="skyway_details">The programme of this event is based on three pillars: Science, Art, People. All with great illuminations to be watched at night</string>
    <string name="sff">Short Film Festival</string>
    <string name="sff_details">The very first festival in Poland entirely devoted to the presentation of short films</string>
    <string name="copernicon">Copernicon</string>
    <string name="copernicon_details">Fantasy Festival, which is visited by fans from all over Poland, is the largest convention in the region and has been taking place in the city since 2010</string>
    <string name="blues">Blues Meeting</string>
    <string name="blues_details">An obligatory festival for fans of blues and all its mergers</string>
    <string name="koncerty">Koncerty Pod Gwiazdami</string>
    <string name="koncerty_details">The festival Concerts under the Stars consists of several concerts that take place on summer evenings, also outdoors</string>
    <string name="forte">Forte Artus Festival</string>
    <string name="forte_details">Meetings with known artists, concerts of a very diverse nature and performance, also spectacles</string>
    <string name="lalek">International Festival of Puppet Theaters</string>
    <string name="lalek_details">Several theaters from different corners of Europe meet to show performances whose main aspect is animation</string>
    <string name="tofifest">Tofifest</string>
    <string name="tofifest_details">International Film Festival with productions awarded in Berlin, Cannes or Locarno and promising debuts</string>
    <string name="monuments">Monuments</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="bars">Bars</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Drawer Opened</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Drawer Closed</string>
</resources>
